free-articles-zone.com 2010-05-14

# Free articles privacy policy

_Overview  
_Free-Articles-Zone Free reprint articles privacy policy deals with the treatment of personal information that is recorded when you use our website. The information included is what you feed into the online forms, plus automatic information (ip, software and hardware) which is used for site analytics purposes.

Our privacy policy relates only to Free-Articles-Zone website, and does not include any linked (Authors') websites or websites linking to Free-Articles-Zone (Publishers' websites).

_Information sharing and disclosure  
_Free-Articles-Zone will never release or sell your information to any 3rd party whatsoever. Our newsletters and e-mails will always include an opt-out option, giving you the option to remove yourself from further Free-Articles-Zone newsletters and announcements.

_Cookies_  
Our website only uses session ID cookies for advertisement distribution purposes. These cookies expire when the session does.  
a.. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
b.. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.  
c.. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

_Security_  
Your email address information is stored in a protected directory -  Access is restricted to Free-Articles-Zone staff. 

_Notification of Changes  
_Free-Articles-Zone will occasionally update our Privacy Policy. If there are any major privacy policy changes, we will publish them on the website. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.
